tipspit.com 2018-02-08

# Privacy Policy

Personal data is information that relates to or is capable of identifying a living person.

Your privacy is paramount to us. At TipsPit.com we have a few fundamentally simple principles:

  * To create an account, you simply select a user name/password and you are good to go. We don’t ask you for personal information, no e-mail, no address, nothing else, unless you want to add an e-mail in case you forget your password.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We believe “One Good Tip Can Change a Life” and because of it, we believe you will come back to the site on your own. We don’t store your personal information on TipsPit.com servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

_Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:_  
If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team at support@Tipspit.com  
As stated above, the Account Holder’s privacy is very important to us and we do all we can to protect it. The main purpose of this Privacy Policy is to make you aware of the information we may gather about you, how we may use it, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. Words and phrases in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in the TipsPit.com Terms and Conditions Agreement. 

###  General Information

When you join TipsPit.com your personal data will be collected, processed, stored and used by us to provide customer support and for other purposes referred to in this Privacy Policy, the TipsPit.com Terms and Conditions Agreement and any other agreements that Account Holders may have with us. 

###  The information we collect

**Personal data:** When you first sign-up for TipsPit.com, we ask for your user name/password and that is all you need to provide in order to join. We don’t force you to provide your e-mail address; it is optional, as is any other personal information we may ask you for. In addition we usually also capture your IP address. The amount and type of information that Tipspit.com gathers depends on the nature of your interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username/password but the e-mail address is optional. If you use your Facebook, Twitter, or other social networking site’s account information to sign in to Tipspit, we will collect and store your SNS user ID and related information. You may also create a Topic, provide a tip under someone else’s topic or simply provide a topic less tip. These contributions are publicly viewable on Tipspit.com, along with your user name. This information may be collected by search engines and republished elsewhere on the Web. We will retain your personal data for as long as is permitted for legal, regulatory, spam and fraud prevention purposes.

**Cookies:** When your web browser accesses a specific web site such as ours, cookies (a type of small text file) may, depending on your browser settings, be automatically stored on your computer's hard drive. From time to time, Tipspit.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

###  Cookies on the TipsPit.com website do the following:

  * Tell us the route (such as a web-search or an online advertisement, for example) by which you came to the TipsPit.com site. Where you are an Account Holder: 
  * Keep you logged in to your Account for a period of time.
  * Allow us to comply with your choices about the display of information in your Account.
  * Track your use of Tips functionality available throughout the TipsPit.com site.
  * Remember the options you select.
  * Permit integration with social media sites (such as the ability to "like" TipsPit.com on Facebook, Twitter and other social networks).
  * We believe that the cookies you encounter on the TipsPit.com site are either (i) necessary to perform the functions that Account Holders wish to use the TipsPit.com Service for, or (ii) are non-intrusive.
  * To learn how to manage and remove cookies, please go to www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies.

_Please note, however, that if you set your browser to reject cookies you may not be able to use certain features of TipsPit.com_

### Security

We're committed to protecting your personal information. All information that you provide to us is stored on secure servers and access to this database is restricted internally. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we use reduce the possibility of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.  
Access to your Account is password-protected for your privacy and security. While we do our best to protect your personal information, you must also protect yourself. What does this mean?  
Keep your password or other access information secret.  
Ensure no-one else uses TipsPit.com while your machine is "signed in" to the TipsPit.com site. Make sure you sign out from your Account when not using it. 

### Sharing

We may share (whether or not for payment) aggregated demographic information with our partners, clients and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  
We may also use such aggregated information and statistics for monitoring the Website usage in order to help us develop the Website and our services, and may provide such aggregate information to third parties.  

### Editing your Account and mailing settings

We like to keep in touch with our Account Holders so after you have signed up to TipsPit.com we'll send you information about Tips/Topics or services provided by us.  
Of course we know receiving a lot of e-mails can be annoying so we try to keep ours to a minimum. However, if you feel you're getting too many or would like more you can change the settings in your Account at any time. Each communication gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving similar future communications. You can review, change or correct your identity and e-mail address information by signing into your Account and going to the settings tab.  
Please note there are some communications that are an integral part of the TipsPit.com and cannot be opted-out of. These communications cover, amongst other things, changes to TipsPit.com and your actual or potential transactions.
